whichvoip.com 2019-08-21

# Privacy Policy | WhichVoIP

_Last Updated: February 8th, 2019_

**www.whichvoip.com("WhichVoIP", "we", "our")** is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors on-line while interacting with the content, products and services on this site (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other web sites to which we link. This Privacy Policy describes in some detail the information that we collect from you ( **or "User"** ) as part of the normal operation of our service, and what may happen to the information we collect.

You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

## Information Collected

When you visit Site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information ("Personal Information") you voluntarily choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information ("Website Information") collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Site. 

  1. Personal Information

    1. Registration Information:   
When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself such as Full Name, Gender, Location and Address.

    2. Credit Card Information:   
If you choose to avail of our services, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:  
Name  
Mailing Address  
Email Address  
Credit Card Numer such as name on credit card, credit card billing address and business and home phone number. 

    3. Email Information:   
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

  2. Website Information

Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and web server log files to collect information about how our Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the IP address, browser types, date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Site, and the web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. 

## Use of Information Obtained

We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications, by email, regarding new services offered by us that we think you may find valuable.

Please note that Personal Information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features. 

We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyze data such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand our Site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

You will receive notice when your Personal Information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

We may also work with outside companies to provide you with customized advertising or content. Your Personal Information and Website Information may be shared with these companies. However we will not allow these companies to share your Personal Information with any third party or from using it for any other purpose. 

## Use of Review Submission Information

By submitting a review on this Site the User permits the Site to use this information for validating that the User submitting the review is a current, or previous, customer of the Service Provider in review. This may include sharing some or all of the information obtained from the review submission with the service provider under review for verification purposes to help mitigate false review submissions.

## Email/ Newsletter Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive our emails or e-newsletter you may opt-out of receiving them by selecting the 'opt out' option located at the bottom of each email and/or e-newsletter. However, we reserve the right to send you notices even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

## Message/Bulletin Boards, Blogs, and Forums

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Message Boards, Blogs, and Forums that the information can be assessed by the public and used by those people to send you unsolicited messages. We shall not be held liable or responsible for any adverse claims thereto. 

## Cookies

We use "cookies". A cookie is a small piece of data stored on the User's computer. We use cookies to identify the Internet browser, store users' preferences, and determine whether the correct software needed to access certain material on the Site has been installed. Data in cookies may also be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services. 

Third party advertisements displayed on the Site may also contain cookies set by advertising companies or advertisers (known as "third party cookies"). We do not control these third party cookies and Users of the Site should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. 

You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Site.

We may use cookies and similar tools to customise the content and advertising you receive based on the Personal Information and Website Information you have provided. The information used for this feature does not provide your Personal Information or identify you as an individual to third parties, but will involve the processing of certain Website Information such as IP addresses. 

## IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. 

## Disclosure of Information

WhichVoIP may share any information you submit on or to the Site when it has your consent to do so.

We **do not** share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a User or subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested. 

WhichVoIP aggregates non-personally identifiable information and may disclose such aggregated information to third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, it does not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you. 

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or We believe that such action is necessary: to comply with legal process such as a search warrant or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorised use of Our Site. 

WhichVoIP may also share or disclose information, where necessary, to legal and other professional advisers, WhichVoIP’s related companies and other business support providers, including document storage, printing and collating companies. 

## Lead Generation

Without advertising support and lead generation, we could not keep the Web site free for use. We share aggregate information with our partners, affiliates and advertisers. We will not share your personally identifiable information with any third party, unless we tell you otherwise when we collect the information or pass on the information for quote generation purposes, you have consented by "opting in" to being contacted by www.whichvoip.com, its partners, third party partners, affiliates or advertisers, or we have informed you of a change to our privacy policy so that you can then choose to opt out.

## Links

You should be aware that when you are on this Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Site pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or a "referral link to another site", the "click" takes you off the Site. This includes links from some advertisers, site sponsors and partners that may use Site's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to Users, collect data or solicit personal information. 

The Site is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a User should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collect by the Site.

## Your Consent

By using our Site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. 

## Data Security

WhichVoIP has established company-wide security practices for your protection. These practices include, but are not limited to, firewall security, the use of appropriate encryption technology, and the use of multiple levels of password security to limit access to data on a "need-to-know" basis. 

We may use contractors or vendors to help us provide some of the services at our site. If we disclose personal information for them to provide the services, it is with the requirement that the information is kept confidential and used only for those services. All contractors and employees are required to familiarize themselves with, and abide by, these safeguards. 

## Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences

We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information for many of our services. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features such as edit and account. 

## Privacy Control

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians. 

## Acquisition or Changes in Ownership

In the event that the Site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. 

## Changes in the Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with the new Privacy Policy, without your prior consent. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please Contact Us.
